STANDARD FOR LIFE
Here is Mr and Mrs Hans Baksteen -
visitors from Holland who are here in the
Synagogue Church of all Nations in Lagos Nigeria,
seeking for the fruit of the womb
from God Almighty.
Mr & Mrs Baksteen
This is a document from the
minister of Justice in Holland
registering their application for adoption of a child.
This proves they have given
up all hope of having their own child.
But today, they are returning to
Jesus Christ, the Giver of life.
You are welcome to the Synagogue
Church of All Nations in Jesus' name.
Tell us your name and the country you come from.
My name is Mrs Baksteen, I'm 31
years old and I'm from Holland.
Who is the man sitting next to you?
The man sitting next to me is my husband.
And the problem that brought me to the Synagogue
is the problem of looking for the fruit of the womb.
I went twice through some surgery and
they had some research.
And they found out that there was a problem,
which they couldn't find as specific.
But there was a problem in having babies though.
My husband is having a problem of
low sperm count so that's the reason and
that this combination of my problem and his
problem makes it very very difficult
to have our own baby.
This is my second visit and the first
visit I discussed this with the prophet.
I told him that we were in the process of adopting
and that this process was about three years.
And he said, "Well, don't continue
the adoption and bring your husband
so you will have your own baby."
Let's hear from your husband.
My name is Hans Baksteen.
The woman beside me is my wife.
I'm in the Synagogue Church of All Nations today
because of the problem of fruit of the womb.
My wife especially went to several hospitals and
had some surgeries in order to get a baby
but there was no solution to it.
When we found out that there was no medical solution,
then we started the process of adoption.
And here you can see the
permission to adopt a baby.
It's a permission form from the ministry of
justice, so it is an official permit to
adopt a baby from another country and we were intending to adopt a child from Ethiopia.
Is this why you came here today?
Yeah, this is why I'm here because I believe that
God is able to solve this problem for us,
and that He can give us a baby.
HEALING TIME
This is the emergency section of
the Synagogue Church of all Nations
where visitors from all over the world have come
to receive a touch from our
Lord and Savior Jesus Christ
through his able servant prophet T.B. Joshua.
Among them are Mr and Mrs Baksteen.
Be healed in Jesus' name.
Here is prophet T.B. Joshua stretching forth this hand
to command out everything that is not of Jesus,
and to replace it with what is of Jesus.
It is God's desire for everyone to
be restored to full and abundant life.
Jesus Christ is now shaking the obstacle
of the problem they have faced for so long.
Lord I believe in Your name
You are free today in the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Time with Jesus is time with joy, as prophet TB Joshua
assures them that their blessing is not far from them.
They now have something to shout "Hallelujah!" about.
A few months later
Mr and Mrs Baksteen came back to
the Synagogue Church of All Nations
to testify that Mrs Baksteen is now pregnant.
To God be the Glory!
TESTIMONY TIME
Jesus Christ says what He means
and He means what He says.
When He says you are blessed,
you are blessed indeed.
Hans and Josein have come singing
and dancing back into the Synagogue
showing the blessing of God in their lives.
Our names are Mr and Mrs Hans and Josein Baksteen.
We are from Holland and the problem that
brought us to the Synagogue Church of All Nations,
was low sperm count and fruit of the womb.
We came to Nigeria and last March
Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for us.
And then we went back to Holland
and we met as husband and wife.
And after that my wife became pregnant
and now you can see her - she is seven
and half months pregnant.
Praise the Lord for that!
And our advice to all people who
are looking for fruit of the womb is,
trust in the Lord and be patient and what
He did for us, He can also do for you.
Praise the Lord!
My name is Josein Baksteen.
I'm all the way from Holland.
And as you can see I'm pregnant now,
here I am standing in front of you for the glory of God
telling you that I'm pregnant and I'm very very happy.
SCOAN Sunday Service
A few months later Mr And Mrs Hans Baksteen
came back to the Synagogue Church
of All Nations with their bouncing baby
to testify to the goodness of God in their lives.
Mr & Mrs Baksteen Arriving At The SCOAN With Their Baby
Mr and Mrs Baksteen are back to
the Synagogue Church of All Nations
with their child which is definitely
something to be happy about.
Glory be to God, they have
received from Jesus Christ.
Mr & Mrs Baksteen Arriving At The SCOAN With Their Baby
Mr and Mrs Hans Baksteen, the blessed parents
are now walking in the midst of the people of God with their newborn
baby to testify that God knows every need you face.
And He is ready to supply them.
So just believe!
Mr & Mrs Baksteen Arriving At The SCOAN With Their Baby
My name is Josein Baksteen.
I'm from Holland.
And the baby's name is Promise Baksteen.
The man sitting next to me
is my husband Hans Baksteen.
When I came to the Synagogue Church of All Nations,
I was very surprised seeing all these miracle babies.
I wasn't even thinking about having
another baby anymore
because we waited for such a long time.
I became very happy because I thought
if God can do this for these people, He can surely do it for us.
We were in the process of adopting a baby,
which is a very long process.
It takes five years to adopt a baby and
we were in this process for three years.
We had all the official papers ready,
the Prophet prayed over the problem -
the problem of fruit of the womb and low sperm count.
He prayed over the problem and we went to home.
We met as husband and wife and
after a while I became pregnant.
Praise the Lord!
In my pregnancy I even visited
the Synagogue Church again
and then I was seven months pregnant,
the prophet said, "You will deliver a
baby girl and her name will be Promise."
So that was a real promise of God.
So as you can see we have
a bouncing baby girl her name is promise.
And we are very very happy.
Praise the Lord!
We thank the Lord for what He
has done in our lives.
He is good, He is so good.
My name is Hans Baksteen,
I'm the husband of Josein
who is sitting beside me.
The name of the baby is Promise Joy Illeri Oluwa.
Mr & Mrs Baksteen With Their Baby Promise
Which means "Promise of God".
The problem that brought us to the Synagogue
was the problem of barrenness.
My part of the problem was low sperm count.
Last year March, I was invited to come
with my wife to the Synagogue Church.
And the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua
prayed over our problem.
After that we went home and we
met as husband and wife.
My wife got pregnant and then after nine months
she delivered a beautiful bouncing
baby girl named Promise of God.
We thank God for what He has done in our lives.
And our advice to couples who are also looking for the fruit of the womb
is that they trust God because He can also do
for them what he has done for us.
Mr & Mrs Baksteen With Their Baby Promise
Baby Promise Crawling
Baby Promise Walking
This is Promise Baksteen.
She's growing stronger day by day
and she is now walking.
Promise is very happy to be back in
the Synagogue Church of All Nations today.
And she's come with her parents
to give God all the glory.
Promise, Now Walking Returns To The SCOAN
TT: Lizz Ndungu ,02:01:2018
RV:Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 30/06/2018